<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on NYCKI Secretary Digest</title>
    <link>https://secscholar.github.io/Digest/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on NYCKI Secretary Digest</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 01:16:12 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://secscholar.github.io/Digest/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>May Update</title>
      <link>https://secscholar.github.io/Digest/posts/mayupdate2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 01:16:12 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://secscholar.github.io/Digest/posts/mayupdate2023/</guid>
      <description>Overview Hello Everyone!
I am reintroducing myself as I don&amp;rsquo;t think many got my first update. My name is Anis Choudhury and I will be serving as the District Secretary for our New York District this 2023-2024 year. I made this site so all the information that I provide over the year will be in one place.
Action Items Election Report Forms As you know the election report form is the only way for district to know what the status of your new club board is.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Internation Convention (ICON) 2023</title>
      <link>https://secscholar.github.io/Digest/posts/icon/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 02:47:41 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://secscholar.github.io/Digest/posts/icon/</guid>
      <description>Overview International Convention is an event where members from all the Circle Ks and Kiwanis across the organization come together to one place.
Event Details Logistical Information Location: Minneapolis, Minnesota at the Minneapolis, Convention Center Date: June 20-24 Registration Due Date: May 25th Registration Costs: $300 (this does not include boarding) Boarding Cost: $433.13 per person Each room was $108.33 per night The event is for 4 days and each room is split between 4 people Event Schedule Wednesday June 21st Time Description 12-4pm Convention Registration Opens 4-6 pm Dinner and Fellowship 6:30-7:30pm Opening Session/Kick-off 7:30-10pm Fellowship (Alumni Event) Thursday June 22nd Time Description 9:30-11:30am Joining KI Workshops and Speakers KI Kickoff and Welcome Parade of Districts CKI take part in the welcome session and stage Clint Pulver, Keynote Speaker 11;30am - 1-pm Lunch and Market place lunch is included 1-4pm KI and CKI Workshops 4-5pm KI Lunachpad Speakers: Cultivating Community 6-10pm Kiwanis Jamboree Hors d&amp;rsquo;oeuvres included Friday June 23rd Time Description 9-11 am Caucus of the Whole 11:30am - 1pm Lunch and the Marketplace lunch is included 1pm - 2pm House of Delegates: Elections only 2-4pm Fellowshipo of Service Project 4-6pm Dinner (on your own) Kiwanis Keynote Speaker &amp;ndash; Andrew Zimmer 6:30-9pm House of Delegates (part 2) 9-11pm Host Committee Social of Fellowship activity Saturday June 23rd Time Description 9-11 am Workshops 11:30am - 1pm Lunch and Marketplace Lunch is included 1:30-4pm Service Project and/or additional Workshops 5-6:30pm Dinner (on your own) 7-10pm Closing/Award Session Doors open at 6:30 Awards, retirement of outgoing board, installation of new officers 9-10pm Closing Reception The event consists of Kiwanis entertainment events Key note speakers and Workshops Service Projects Awards The election for International Positions And you can hang out with all the different Circle Kers away in a place away from home!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Committees Applications (2023)</title>
      <link>https://secscholar.github.io/Digest/posts/committees/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 02:29:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://secscholar.github.io/Digest/posts/committees/</guid>
      <description>Overview Note: Registration is closed!
In Circle K there are a number of Committees that carry out tasks that are needed for the district to run. Through being in these Committees members can get to know the workings of Circle K on a district level and if you become a chair, you can lead entire parts of the district.
Note: If you become a chair, you can hold this positions while still holding a board position on the club level</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>April Update</title>
      <link>https://secscholar.github.io/Digest/posts/aprilupdate2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 01:58:24 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://secscholar.github.io/Digest/posts/aprilupdate2023/</guid>
      <description>Overview Hello Everyone!
My name is Anis Choudhury and I will be serving as the District Secretary for our New York District this 2023-2024 year. I made this site so all the information that I provide over the year will be in one place.
Action Items Membership Update Center This is where secretaries are supposed to submit there monthly report forms. I want to remind all past secretaries to add the new secretaries to the membership update center.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
